Guide to the Josephine Swanson papers, 1970-2008.
Swanson, Josephine
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Josephine Swanson papers, 1970-2008.
23-26-3746
Josephine. Swanson
1.4 cubic feet.
Correspondence, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence, publications, and material pertaining to Cornell Cooperative Extension programs Swanson developed providing professional trainings in food resource management, consumer economics and family resource management.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Assistant Dean in the College of Human Ecology and Associate Director of Cornell Cooperative Extension.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence, publications, and material pertaining to Cornell Cooperative Extension programs Swanson developed providing professional trainings in food resource management, consumer economics and family resource management.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Swanson, Josephine.; Cornell University--Faculty.; Cornell University.Cooperative Extension.; New York State College of Human Ecology--Administration.; New York State College of Human Ecology.Dept. of Policy Analysis and Management.
Subjects:
Consumer behavior.; Consumer education--Study and teaching--New York (State)--Ithaca.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Biographical Material, 2003 - 2006 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- "The CEH Years" - A Biography (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Reappointment Material Collected, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Publications by Swanson, 1983 - 2008 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Conference Presentations, 1977 - 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Awards (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Children and Money - Handouts, 1985 - 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- You're Accountable" - Teaching Materials, 1986 - 1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- "Me and Money" - Inservice, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- "Be a Better Shopper", 1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- "Be a Better Shopper" - Post Inservice Evaluation, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Correspondences and Articles Concerning the Cornell Migrant Progam, 1998 - 2004 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Building an Understanding of Credit Services (BUCS), 1990s (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Building an Understanding of Credit Services - Focus Group Transcripts from the Needs Assessment, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Building an Understanding of Credit Services (BUCS) - VHS Tape (Box 1, Folder 15)
- "Transition to Independent Living: Financial Management for Older and At-Risk Youth" - Satellite Broadcasting, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Extension Program Review, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Building an Understanding of Credit Services - Handouts, 1994 - 1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Reducing Risk and Increasing Capacity (RRIC) - Evaluation Plan and Planning Conference, 1994 - 1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Building an Understanding of Credit Services - Administration, Leader, Training, Working with Learners, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Building an Understanding of Credit Services - Budgeting Basics, Credit Options, Consumer Rights and Responsibilities, Family Communication, Community Resources, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Welfare Reform - Cooperative Extensions Role, 1996 - 1997 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Welfare Reform - Inservices, Memos, Resources, 1996 - 1998, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Welfare Reform, 1998 - 1999 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Welfare Reform, 1998 - 1999 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Welfare Reform, 1998 - 1999 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Head Start - Relationships with Cooperative Extension, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Family Resolutions Project, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Safe and Supportive Communities - Response to Columbine, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Child Care Project - in PAM, 1999 - 2004 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Strategic Plan - Development, 2000 - 2005 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Human Ecology Centennial - Extension Events, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Healthy Families, Healthy Communities: Building Supportive Policies, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- NYS Community Health Partnership, 20001 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Human Ecology Faculty Outreach and Extensino Activity, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Parenting Education, 2001 - 2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- College of Human Ecology Programs Done in Collaboration with Cooperative Extension Professionals, 2002 - 2007 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Cornell Migrant Program Review, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Internal Review of the Cornell Migrant Program, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Responses to the Review of the Cornell Migrant Program, 2003 - 2004 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Agricultural Immigration Policy and Implications - Discussion, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Human Ecology Faculty Outreach and Extension Activity, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Rural Familes Speak Project, 2003 - 2007 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Rural Familes Speak - Basebook Report - North Central Region, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Rural Prosperity: A Longitudinal Study of Rural Communities and Rural Low-Income Familes, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- College of Human Ecology Extension Distance Learning, 2004 - 2008 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Conference Presentation - AAFCS - "FCS Science-based Techniques for Contemporary Emergencies", 2006 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Human Ecology Faculty Outreach and Extension Activity, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Agricultual Science and Education Exhibition - Rural Families Speak: Health and Food Security Exhibit, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Chaos and Children's Development BLCC Distance Learning Event, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 15)